hey this week we are looking at the cake
嘿，这周我们在看蛋糕
ASB 7-inch Raspberry Pi screen case yes
ASB 7英寸Raspberry Pi屏幕保护套是
it's like a big long name but basically
就像一个大名字，但基本上
we've looked at a cake ASB case before
我们之前看过一个ASB蛋糕盒
that has the 13 inch screen yes that
拥有13英寸的屏幕
thing is fantastic but I need something
事情太棒了，但我需要一些东西
a little more portable a little more
多一点便携式
like fit in your bag and take it with
喜欢适合你的包，并与
you wherever you go kind of thing okay
你无论走到哪里都可以
we're all fans of Raspberry Pi here
我们都是Raspberry Pi的粉丝
micro computing and KSP makes some of
微处理器和KSP使
the greatest cases so let's get right
最好的情况，让我们开始吧
into it I'm just gonna jump right down
我要跳进去
here I've got everything I need yeah yup
这里我有我需要的一切，是的
my trusty Raspberry Pi 3b plus I've got
我值得信赖的Raspberry Pi 3b，加上
a can of cat 2.5 amp power supply for
一罐Cat 2.5安培电源，用于
the Raspberry Pi and we've got the case
Raspberry Pi，我们已经知道了
this is from KK SP you can get one at
这是从KK SP那里可以买到的
cap five dot TV slash pie but this is
盖五个点电视斜线馅饼，但这是
not an advertisement this is not late
不是广告，这不晚
night television to try to sell you
夜间电视试图卖给你
something I want to show you but I want
我想给你看的东西，但我想要
to make sure that you have access to it
确保您可以访问它
at the same time so let's get into the
同时，让我们进入
box and let's see the unboxing here
盒子，让我们在这里看到拆箱
we're not unboxing at the unboxing you
我们不会在您拆箱的时候拆箱
know what I'm just gonna do it right
知道我会做正确的事
here Jeff goodness oh wow okay we've got
在这里，Jeff天哪，哦，哇，好了
a lint-free cloth for wiping it down
无绒布，用于擦拭
we've got the manual for a screen so
我们有屏幕手册，所以
this is of course like the last one it's
当然，这就像最后一个
a capacitive touch screen and this one
电容式触摸屏
is just a lot more like tiny oh but at
更像是微小的哦，但是在
the same time it's got the same quality
同时具有相同的质量
that you expect from kks be this is a
您对kks的期望是
let's see here oh it's like stuck to the
让我们在这里看到哦，就像被卡在
tape there we go it works this is a
胶带在那里，我们去工作，这是一个
laser-cut powder-coated high-grade steel
激光切割粉末喷涂高级钢
case this looks amazing
这种情况看起来很棒
very nice right so professional there
非常好，很专业
you go
你走
these are some of the best cases as far
这些是迄今为止最好的一些情况
as the ruggedness and the quality they
作为坚固性和质量
are just fantastic the screen is 1024 by
屏幕真是太棒了1024
600 it is touchscreen and and it
600是触摸屏，
actually is going to well it's going to
实际上会好起来，
connect to a Raspberry Pi right here so
在这里连接到Raspberry Pi
perfect let's see what else is in the
完美，让我们看看还有什么
box and then let's
盒子，然后让我们
about what it takes to get this thing
关于得到这个东西需要什么
set up so we've got cables here very
设置好，所以我们在这里有电缆
important very important hmm a nice
非常重要非常重要
short HDMI cable to connect the screen
短的HDMI电缆连接屏幕
which is nice because it rather than
很好，因为它比
having a big long length that you've got
拥有很长的长度
a wrap up comes with that one
一个包裹一起来
we've got USB which I don't see a power
我们有USB，我看不到电源
cord for this particular screen so I
该特定屏幕的电源线，所以我
imagine that the USB is going to not
想象一下USB不会
only provide the touch screen
只提供触摸屏
capabilities but also the power to the
能力，还有力量
seven-inch screen of Salomon and then
所罗门的七英寸屏幕，然后
we've got some screws they're always fun
我们有一些螺丝钉，它们总是很有趣
but not a little bit there and an allen
但那里一点儿也没有艾伦
key and I'm sure my name and we've got
键，我确定我的名字，我们已经
the the actual stand as well for nice
实际的立场也很好
for a level surface okay so let's get
一个水平的表面好吧，让我们开始吧
into this guy right here so we've got
进入这个家伙，所以我们有
that's not the one let's see we've got
那不是一个让我们看到的
an allen key right here I'd like you to
我想要一个内六角扳手
meet my friend Alan now let's pull this
认识我的朋友艾伦，现在让我们拉一下
thing apart
分开的东西
all right so with this be easier than
好吧，这样比
building IKEA furniture so far
目前为止正在制造宜家家具
definitely yes I kind of like that it
绝对是的，我有点喜欢
doesn't come in pieces mm-hmm it comes
不会散成mm-hmm
assembled so I can see exactly how it's
组装起来，所以我可以确切地看到它是如何
gonna go back together Henry okay I'd
一起回去亨利，好吧，我会
like to point out nobody's read the
想指出没有人读过
manual yet was there a manual well the
手册，但是有手册吗
manuals for the screen thing how
屏幕东西手册如何
difficult is it good what is the screen
困难是什么好，屏幕是什么
manual tells on the back note you need
手册告诉您需要的背面说明
to first connect the USB cable before
首先连接USB电缆
the HDMI cable otherwise the backlight
HDMI电缆，否则背光
may cannot turn on maybe not so that's
可能无法打开，也许无法打开，所以
for the screen itself
屏幕本身
yes but had you've done it the other way
是的，但是您是否已经做了另一种方式
you would have been like oh it doesn't
你会一直想，哦，那不是
work we're in Jeff we've got a couple of
我们在杰夫工作，我们有几个
standoffs here just pulling those off
僵局在这里只是拉那些
with my fingers wow the big motion this
用我的手指哇这大动作
is impressive oh yeah yes
令人印象深刻哦是的
I will believe you there Jeff will
我会相信你，杰夫会
translate our manual for us there we are
我们为我们翻译手册
okay let's get into our Raspberry Pi 3
好吧，让我们进入我们的Raspberry Pi 3
B+ all right fresh out of the box fresh
B +可以开箱即用
out of the box nice come on now
开箱即用，不错，快点来
there we are all right and that is gonna
那里我们没事，那将会
go right in there just like we expect
就像我们期望的那样去那里
from k KS B it is just that a beautiful
从k KS B就是那美丽
perfect fit standoffs are gonna go back
完美的对峙将要回去
on I have no clue what potente o meter
我不知道什么电表
is potentiometer oh now we know close
是电位器哦，现在我们知道了关闭
that does not look like that at all
根本不像那样
did you leaders and apparently there's
你有领导吗，显然有
ghost problems oh don't ghost me are you
鬼问题哦，别鬼我是你
gonna call there we are
要打电话给我们
well if it's in there nice quite nicely
好吧，如果它在那里很好
oh yeah
哦耶
now obviously this won't work for a
现在显然这将不适用于
Raspberry Pi with the fam you'd have to
Raspberry Pi与您必须拥有的家族
use the heatsink now why do you think
现在使用散热器为什么你认为
that Jeff you said obviously so I want
杰夫，你说的很明显，所以我想
to know what makes it seem obvious well
知道什么使它看起来很明显
it's a metal case and it doesn't have
这是金属外壳，没有
the hole for the fan my dear friend how
粉丝的洞我亲爱的朋友
where does the fan connector that's how
风扇连接器在哪里
do you mean power no no where are you
你的意思是力量吗？不，你在哪里？
gonna put the fan in so to screw it in
会把风扇放进去以便拧紧
yeah well this goes on top yeah I will
是的，这很重要，是的，我会
have you nice little fan yeah you could
你有个好小风扇吗
but when you do couldn't you just have
但是当你做不到的时候
one that is built into the heatsink I
内置在散热器中的一个
would I think it's still meant for the
我想这仍然意味着
for the heatsink I don't know okay like
对于散热器，我不知道像
I'm trying to think my Raspberry Pi at
我正在尝试认为我的Raspberry Pi在
home with a fan I don't think the fan
带风扇的家，我不认为风扇
would fit because it's one that you
会适合，因为这是你的一个
screw into it yeah case
拧进去，是的
oh yeah that's a little different in
哦，是的，有点不同
that case Jeff what I would do if you
杰夫，如果你，我会怎么做
wanted to put a fan on here yeah is that
想在这里放个风扇，是的，
we just put a little bit of 3m
我们只放了一点3m
double-sided tape on the fan just around
风扇周围的双面胶带
the edge of the fan and then you can
风扇的边缘，然后您就可以
actually stick the fan on here that's
其实把风扇放在这里
gonna hold it nice and snug
会保持它的舒适
if you don't have double sided tape a
如果您没有双面胶
little bit of hot glue that'll hold it
一点点热胶将它固定住
there yep that works fair enough
是的，足够公平
alright so let's all right put the case
好吧，让我们没事了
back on there we are we've got the
回到那里，我们有了
Raspberry Pi 3 B+ in its place
Raspberry Pi 3 B +取代了它
there we are
我们在那里
line that up looking professional oh
排队那看起来专业哦
yeah say welcome back to Linden was in
是的，欢迎回到林登
the chat real in then very long time
在很长的时间内真正的聊天
yeah good to have you back dude alright
是的，很高兴你回来，伙计，好的
put those screws in this is some
把那些螺丝放在这是一些
exciting TV right here I can almost just
令人兴奋的电视在这里我几乎可以
tell you wow the screws to hold this all
告诉你哇，螺丝钉可以固定住这一切
together we don't necessarily have to
在一起，我们不一定非要
put them together
放在一起
live on the air but I can you you you
直播，但我可以你吗
pay attention to those small details
注意那些小细节
those little details details riveting
那些小细节使铆钉细节化
nature of cat5 it is look at those
cat5的性质是看那些
screws beep look at that folks
螺丝蜂鸣声看看那个人
tentative because we're live I can't
暂时的，因为我们活着，我不能
even speed it up you know there we are
甚至加快速度，你知道我们在那里
and you just kind of feel your way with
而您只是觉得自己的方式
these big long screws right and get that
这些大长螺丝正确，并得到
I just feel so excited we go about all
我只是感到非常兴奋，我们竭尽全力
the potential uses for this yeah you
这个的潜在用途
know with this I mean as I'm looking at
知道这个意思是我在看
it my first thought is a photo frame you
我首先想到的是相框
don't want to be perfect for that but a
不想做到完美，但是
smart photo frame yeah how about that
智能相框是的
something that connects to a server and
连接到服务器的东西
grabs your photos from the server
从服务器抓取您的照片
yeah and rotates through them or could
是的，并通过他们旋转或可以
you even write a scrip for the PI to
您甚至为PI写了一份纸条
pull it from say like your Facebook or
从像你的Facebook或说
Instagram sure yeah and that way as you
Instagram肯定是的，就像你一样
go live with new photos they update
与他们更新的新照片一起上线
instantly you can have it searched
马上就可以搜索到
through your photos for certain tags
通过您的照片中的某些标签
yeah in the descriptions see that would
是的，在说明中看到
work for safe it's all there is to up
安全起见，这就是一切
for odd maybe like an elderly parent or
奇怪的是，可能像年迈的父母或
grandparent that doesn't have facebook
没有Facebook的祖父母
that wants to get constant updates
想要不断更新
photos so the thing to remember with
照片，所以要记住的东西
this job is it is a full Linux computer
这是一台完整的Linux计算机
that is true so nothing to it it's it's
那是真的，所以没有什么是
literally Linux so and it's a computer
从字面上看，Linux就是一台计算机
it's not just a screen anything yeah all
不仅仅是屏幕，是的，所有
right
对
so then finally we've got this guy on
所以最后我们有了这个人
the back just gonna screw that together
后面会拧在一起
okay her small business or something you
好吧，她的小生意或你的事
set up a kiosk or looks I like that idea
设置一个售货亭或看起来我喜欢这个主意
if you just want like a little tablet
如果你只想要一个小平板电脑
you're on that's right it could be so
你是对的，可能是这样
many things what I do like is that it
我喜欢做的很多事情是
has the screw holes on the base mount as
在底座上有螺孔
well so that you can secure it mm-hmm
好，以便您可以固定它mm-hmm
you know depending on what you're using
你知道的取决于你使用的是什么
it for it's not going to move around so
因为它不会移动
what Jeff is talking about as I sew
我缝的时候杰夫在说什么
sophisticatedly put this together for
精巧地将它们组合在一起
you I mean I'm doing this kind of on the
你我的意思是我正在做这种
side as the guys are talking so I mean
伙计们在说话，所以我的意思是
you can imagine it's not very difficult
你可以想象这不是很难
to assemble right I'm doing my thing
正确组装我正在做我的事情
what Jeff's talking about is if you were
杰夫在说的是
to use this in a business environment or
在商业环境中使用它或
a school environment you don't want
你不想要的学校环境
someone walking off with it and it
有人与它走开
actually has screw holes so we've got
实际上有螺丝孔，所以我们有
three screw holes we can actually mount
我们可以实际安装的三个螺丝孔
this on the counter in such a way that
在柜台上以这种方式
nobody can walk off with it there you go
没有人可以走下去，你去
Yeti wizard asks how is this display
雪人向导询问该显示如何
different than the stock pie display so
与股票饼图显示不同
if you get the stock pie display or
如果您看到股票饼图显示，或
anything else is it capacitive touch
还有什么是电容式触摸
this screen is I mean this is the the
这个屏幕是我的意思是这是
wave share touch screen so we know the
波共享触摸屏，所以我们知道
wave share makes some excellent screens
浪潮分享使一些出色的屏幕
I'm not going to I've got two more
我不会再有两个
screws to put in but I just want to kind
螺丝，但我只想种
of expedite things it's solid so but
的东西很扎实所以
what we're looking at here is yeah this
我们在这里看的是这个
guy all right so we've got USB for power
好的，所以我们有USB供电
and that's gonna go in here that also
那将要进入这里
gives us the touch capability now did
给我们现在的触摸功能
you do it in proper fashion
你以适当的方式做
well I plugged it in first Jeff didn't
好吧，我先插了杰夫没有
use me before the HDMI you did it
在使用HDMI之前先使用我
doesn't matter excellent doesn't matter
没关系优秀没关系
power explodes in my hands all this left
力量在我手中爆炸
is the little stand that's awesome here
这里的小摊位很棒
we go all right so some would look at
我们走的很好，所以有些人会看
this and say okay that's a little bit
这个说好一点
janky because you've got these cables
简直是因为您有这些电缆
sticking out the side right yeah there's
伸出侧面，是的，
something that I love about that it'll
我喜欢的东西会
work with any SBC that you can connect
与您可以连接的任何SBC一起使用
to it better so keep in mind if you want
更好，所以请牢记
to do Raspberry Pi 3 B+ like I'm doing
像我一样做Raspberry Pi 3 B +
here today it's gonna work perfectly but
今天在这里会完美工作，但
what if you want to go with like a
如果你想和一个人一起去怎么办
Anasuya
Anasuya
tinker board which is gonna fit this
将适合此的修补板
case to cool that's right yeah you're
冷却的情况是正确的是的，你是
not limited to the I oh yeah you're not
不限于我哦，是的，你不是
limited to the capabilities of a
仅限于
particular proprietary cable that only
仅专用的专用电缆
works on Raspberry Pi right so there you
可以在Raspberry Pi上运行，所以在那里
have it that's all there is to assembly
拥有组装所需的一切
now in the instructions there is a
现在在说明中有一个
little bit of code that you need to add
您需要添加的一点代码
to raspbian there's a config that you
要树莓派，有一个配置，你
need to add it's right here so you just
需要添加它就在这里，所以你只是
open up the file the on your boot
打开您的启动文件
partition and add four lines of code in
分区并在其中添加四行代码
nope at five
五点钟不行
yeah five yes instructions right there
是的，五个是的指示就在那里
yep there it is so hold on to that
是的，所以坚持下去
because you will need the instructions
因为您将需要说明
to add that little bit of code and all
添加一点点的代码和所有
that does is it sets the resolution to
就是将分辨率设置为
1024 by 600 it sets it to HDMI mode 87
1024 x 600将其设置为HDMI模式87
and it and it sets the position of the
它设置了位置
screen and the overscan so that you
屏幕和过扫描，以便您
don't have black borders around on the
周围没有黑色边框
screen okay
屏幕还好
but more importantly it forces you to
但更重要的是，它迫使您
read the manual there's five lines the
阅读手册有五行内容
five lines in the manual that's all you
手册中只有五行
need but make sure you plug in the USB
需要，但请确保您已插入USB
first otherwise as Henry explained it
首先否则，就像亨利解释的那样
will explode these are the KSP seven
将会爆炸的是KSP七
inch screen cases I can't really give
寸屏幕保护套，我真的不能给
you the impression that I have of it
你给我的印象
other than like this is rugged this
除了像这样坚固
feels I mean this is professional it
感觉我是说这很专业
looks professional it's much more solid
看起来很专业，更扎实
it's not there's no plastic seen here
不是这里没有塑料
the cables you can tuck them in as best
您可以将电缆最好塞进去的电缆
you can but you can also just get like
你可以，但你也可以像
an L connector right like an L yeah you
像L一样的L型连接器
could do that minimize it I don't mind
可以做到这一点，我不介意
the cables because I like the fact that
电缆，因为我喜欢这样的事实
I can use this for anything and you can
我可以用它做任何事情，你可以
in fact because this full-sized HDMI
实际上是因为这种全尺寸HDMI
unplug the Raspberry Pi and use this as
拔下Raspberry Pi并将其用作
a screen for any HDMI device and then
任何HDMI设备的屏幕，然后
plug it back in again and you're back to
再次插回电源，您将回到
using it as a Raspberry Pi nice so it is
用它作为树莓派很好
not compatible with the Raspberry Pi 4
与Raspberry Pi 4不兼容
out of the box and that is because
开箱即用，那是因为
Raspberry Pi 4 has a different placement
Raspberry Pi 4具有不同的位置
of the HDMI outputs plus it's a micro
的HDMI输出加上一个微型
HDMI vs and two of them versus a
HDMI vs和其中两个vs
full-sized HD
全尺寸高清
my so it's not that you couldn't fan
我的不是你不能扇
dangle something to make it work if
悬挂一些东西使其工作，如果
you've got the ability to cut steel you
你有能力切割钢材
would be able to punch a little hole to
可以打一个小孔
be able to make it so that it works with
能够做到，使其与
a Raspberry Pi for there's no limit to
一个树莓派，因为没有限制
like the screen will work with it yep
就像屏幕可以正常工作
but the case itself because it's built
但案例本身，因为它是内置的
for a Raspberry Pi 3 B+ and before
适用于Raspberry Pi 3 B +及更高版本
that's the type of output for the HDMI
这是HDMI输出的类型
that the case is compatible with ok so
该案例与确定兼容，所以
that's what we're up against with the
这就是我们要面对的
Raspberry Pi 4 but it's not to say that
Raspberry Pi 4，但这并不是说
you couldn't do a little bit of nice
你不能做点好事
hardware hacking to make it work sounds
硬件骇客使其听起来像声音
like a challenge
像一个挑战
let's make it so then we can like
让我们做到这一点，然后我们就可以喜欢
control a drone or something ooh let's
控制无人驾驶飞机或其他东西
just order let's get on that code it's a
只需订购，让我们获取该代码，这是一个
full computer guys so I mean come up
全电脑的家伙，所以我的意思是
with some ideas let us know how you
有一些想法让我们知道你
would use this is it a kiosk is it a
会用它吗？
little computer to be playing games on
小电脑在玩游戏
is it something that you want to be it's
这是你想成为的东西吗
touchscreen so hey you could use that I
触摸屏，所以您可以使用我
could install Google remote desktop on
可以在以下位置安装Google远程桌面
that and I could control Telestream
那我可以控制Telestream
Wirecast using a touchscreen
使用触摸屏进行有线广播
there you go on a Raspberry Pi I like
在那里，您喜欢我喜欢的Raspberry Pi
that in real time now you could use a
现在您可以实时使用
USB to hook up to say a webcam sure and
USB连接确定网络摄像头，然后
you could use that for video
您可以将其用于视频
conferencing that's true too yeah that
会议也是如此
would be a great little
会很棒
videoconferencing unit can I get like a
视频会议单元我可以像
little command and control center for
小指挥与控制中心
your house yeah or your basement there
是你的房子还是那里的地下室
you go I'm sure game hold from a marrow
你走吧，我敢肯定，这是骨髓的比赛
drive we came up with something cool
开车我们想到了很酷的东西
that guy just like yeah zombify is ever
像是僵尸一样的家伙永远
set to it it's set to it all right folks
设置为它，它设置为所有好人
get yours a cat5 TV /pi we've got some
给你的cat5电视/ pi我们有一些
links there in order to to take a look
链接以查看
at those and we've got the purchase
在那些，我们有购买
links and more information as well
链接以及更多信息